export const beninQuiz = [
  {
    question: "What is the official language of Benin?",
    options: ["English", "French", "Spanish", "Portuguese"],
    correct_answer: "French",
    difficulty: "easy",
  },
  {
    question: "True or False: Benin is located in West Africa.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    correct_answer: "True",
    difficulty: "easy",
  },
  {
    question: "Which city is the capital of Benin?",
    options: ["Porto-Novo", "Cotonou", "Parakou", "Abomey"],
    correct_answer: "Porto-Novo",
    difficulty: "easy",
  },
  {
    question: "Which body of water borders Benin to the south?",
    options: ["Atlantic Ocean", "Indian Ocean", "Red Sea", "Mediterranean Sea"],
    correct_answer: "Atlantic Ocean",
    difficulty: "easy",
  },
  {
    question: "True or False: Benin was formerly known as Dahomey.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    correct_answer: "True",
    difficulty: "easy",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the primary religion practiced in Benin?",
    options: ["Islam", "Christianity", "Vodoun", "Buddhism"],
    correct_answer: "Vodoun",
    difficulty: "medium",
  },
  {
    question: "Which famous Beninese artist is known for the song 'Adouke'?",
    options: ["Angelique Kidjo", "Simi", "Yemi Alade", "Tiwa Savage"],
    correct_answer: "Angelique Kidjo",
    difficulty: "medium",
  },
  {
    question: "True or False: The W National Park is located in Benin.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    correct_answer: "True",
    difficulty: "medium",
  },
  {
    question: "Which river forms part of the border between Benin and Niger?",
    options: ["Niger River", "Volta River", "Zambezi River", "Senegal River"],
    correct_answer: "Niger River",
    difficulty: "easy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "True or False: Benin's economy is heavily reliant on agriculture.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    correct_answer: "True",
    difficulty: "medium",
  },
  {
    question: "Which Beninese city is known for its role in the Slave Trade?",
    options: ["Ouidah", "Cotonou", "Porto-Novo", "Abomey"],
    correct_answer: "Ouidah",
    difficulty: "hard",
  },
  {
    question: "True or False: Benin has a coastline along the Atlantic Ocean.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    correct_answer: "True",
    difficulty: "hard",
  },
];
